https://prometheum.ca/terms-of-service/

Terms of Service - Prometheum Institute
(416) 487-3775, 1-855-233-0370
contact@prometheum.ca
Building mental health through self-realization and self-actualization
Login
Username
Password
Remember Me
Forgot?
Forget your password?
Username or E-mail
Remembered Password?
1. Your Acceptance
By using or visiting the Prometheum Institute website and using the Understanding Change software, data feeds, and services provided to you on, from, or through Prometheum Institute (collectively the “Service”) you signify your agreement to (1) these terms and conditions (the “Terms of Service”), (2) Prometheum Institute privacy policy, found at https://www.prometheum.ca/privacy-policy-2 and incorporated herein by reference. If you do not agree to any of these terms, the Prometheum Institute Policy, or the Community Guidelines, please do not use the Service.
Although we may attempt to notify you when major changes are made to these Terms of Service, you should periodically review the most up-to-date version https://www.prometheum.ca/terms-of-use. Prometheum Institute may, in its sole discretion, modify or revise these Terms of Service and policies at any time, and you agree to be bound by such modifications or revisions. Nothing in these Terms of Service shall be deemed to confer any third-party rights or benefits.
2. Service.
These Terms of Service apply to all users of the Service, The Service includes all aspects of Understanding Change as a self-directed educational program, including but not limited to all products, software and services offered via the Prometheum Institute website, such as the “Lessons”, the “Casual Chats,” the “Message Box” and other applications.
The Service may contain links to third party websites that are not owned or controlled by Prometheum Institute, for instance, PayPal for billing purposes. Prometheum Institute has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party websites. In addition, Prometheum Institute will not and cannot censor or edit the content of any third-party site. By using the Service, you expressly relieve Prometheum Institute from any and all liability arising from your use of any third-party website.
Accordingly, we encourage you to be aware when you leave the Service and to read the terms and conditions and privacy policy of each other website that you visit. In order to access some features of the Service, you will have to create an account within the Prometheum Institute website. You may never use another person’s account without permission as such use allows access to all private information stored in that person’s Message Box. You also are advised not to share your account information with others you do not want to read your private information. When creating your account, you must provide accurate and complete information. You are solely responsible for the activity that occurs on your account, and you must keep your account password secure. You must notify Prometheum Institute immediately (by telephone: 416-487-3775, by email: concerned@prometheum.ca, or be fax: 416-487-9628) of any breach of security or unauthorized use of your account.
Although Prometheum Institute will not be liable for your losses caused by any unauthorized use of your account, you may be liable for the losses of Prometheum Institute or others due to such unauthorized use.
4. General Use of the Service—Permissions and Restrictions
Prometheum Institute hereby grants you permission to access and use the Service as set forth in these Terms of Service, provided that:
You agree not to distribute in any medium any part of the Service or the Content without Prometheum Institute’s prior written authorization, unless Prometheum Institute makes available the means for such distribution through functionality offered by the Service.
You agree not to alter or modify any part of the Service.
You agree not to access Content through any technology or means other than the video playback pages of the Service itself, or other explicitly authorized means Prometheum Institute may designate.
You agree not to use the Service for any of the following commercial uses:
the sale of access to the Service;
the sale of advertising, sponsorships, or promotions placed on or within the Service or Content; or the sale of advertising, sponsorships, or promotions on any page of an ad-enabled blog or website containing Content delivered via the Service, unless other material not obtained from Prometheum Institute appears on the same page and is of sufficient value to be the basis for such sales.
You agree not to use or launch any automated system, including without limitation, “robots,” “spiders,” or “offline readers,” that accesses the Service in a manner that sends more request messages to the Prometheum Institute’s servers in a given period of time than a human can reasonably produce in the same period by using a conventional on-line web browser. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Prometheum Institute grants the operators of public search engines permission to use spiders to copy materials from the site for the sole purpose of and solely to the extent necessary for creating publicly available searchable indices of the materials, but not caches or archives of such materials. Prometheum Institute reserves the right to revoke these exceptions either generally or in specific cases. You agree not to collect or harvest any personally identifiable information, including account names, from the Service, nor to use the communication systems provided by the Service (e.g., comments, email) for any commercial solicitation purposes. You agree not to solicit, for commercial purposes, any users of the Service with respect to their Content.
In your use of the Service, you will comply with all applicable laws.
Prometheum Institute reserves the right to discontinue any aspect of the Service at any time.
5. Your Use of Content
In addition to the general restrictions above, the following restrictions and conditions apply specifically to your use of Content.
The Content on the Service, and the trademarks, service marks and logos (“Marks”) on the Service, are owned by or licensed to Prometheum Institute, subject to copyright and other intellectual property rights under the law.
Content is provided to you AS IS. You may access Content for your information and personal use solely as intended through the provided functionality of the Service and as permitted under these Terms of Service. You can download any Content but you shall not copy, reproduce, distribute, transmit, broadcast, display, sell, license, or otherwise exploit any Content for any other purposes without the prior written consent of Prometheum Institute or the respective licensors of the Content. Prometheum Institute and its licensors reserve all rights not expressly granted in and to the Service and the Content.
You agree not to circumvent, disable or otherwise interfere with security-related features of the Service or features that prevent or restrict use or copying of any Content or enforce limitations on use of the Service or the Content therein.
7. Account Termination Policy
Accounts are permanent. You can come back anytime for a refresher or to read updates.
9. Warranty Disclaimer
YOU AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES SHALL BE AT YOUR SOLE DISCRETION AND THAT THIS IS AN EDUCATIONAL WEBSITE, NOT A COUNSELING SITE. YOU ARE GIVEN INFORMATION THAT HAS BEEN RESEARCHED AND/OR LOGICALLY DEDUCED FROM CURRENTLY ACCUTRATE RESEARCH INFORMATION. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, UNDERSTANDINGCHANGE, ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AND AGENTS DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, IN CONNECTION WITH THE SERVICES AND YOUR USE THEREOF. PROMETHEUM INSTITUTE MAKES NO WARRANTIES OR REPRESENTATIONS ABOUT THE COMPLETENESS OF THIS SITE’S CONTENT AND ASSUMES NO LIABILITY OR RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY (I) ERRORS, MISTAKES, OR INACCURACIES OF CONTENT, (II) PERSONAL INJURY OR PROPERTY DAMAGE, OF ANY NATURE WHATSOEVER, RESULTING FROM YOUR ACCESS TO AND USE OF OUR SERVICES, (III) ANY UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR USE OF OUR SECURE SERVERS AND/OR ANY AND ALL PERSONAL INFORMATION AND/OR FINANCIAL INFORMATION STORED THEREIN, (IV) ANY INTERRUPTION OR CESSATION OF TRANSMISSION TO OR FROM OUR SERVICES, (IV) ANY BUGS, VIRUSES, TROJAN HORSES, OR THE LIKE WHICH MAY BE TRANSMITTED TO OR THROUGH OUR SERVICES BY ANY THIRD PARTY, AND/OR (V) ANY ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN ANY CONTENT OR FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE OF ANY KIND INCURRED AS A RESULT OF THE USE OF ANY CONTENT POSTED, EMAILED, TRANSMITTED, OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE VIA THE SERVICES. UNDERSTANDINGCHANGE DOES NOT WARRANT, ENDORSE, GUARANTEE, OR ASSUME RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY PRODUCT OR SERVICE ADVERTISED OR OFFERED BY A THIRD PARTY THROUGH THE SERVICES OR ANY HYPERLINKED SERVICES OR FEATURED IN ANY BANNER OR OTHER ADVERTISING, AND UNDERSTANDINGCHANGE WILL NOT BE A PARTY TO OR IN ANY WAY BE RESPONSIBLE FOR MONITORING ANY TRANSACTION BETWEEN YOU AND THIRD-PARTY PROVIDERS OF PRODUCTS OR SERVICES.
10. Limitation of Liability
IN NO EVENT SHALL PROMETHEUM INSTITUTE, ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, OR AGENTS, BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM ANY (I) ERRORS, MISTAKES, OR INACCURACIES OF CONTENT, (II) PERSONAL INJURY OR PROPERTY DAMAGE, OF ANY NATURE WHATSOEVER, RESULTING FROM YOUR ACCESS TO AND USE OF OUR SERVICES, (III) ANY UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR USE OF OUR SECURE SERVERS AND/OR ANY AND ALL PERSONAL INFORMATION AND/OR FINANCIAL INFORMATION STORED THEREIN, (IV) ANY INTERRUPTION OR CESSATION OF TRANSMISSION TO OR FROM OUR SERVICES, (IV) ANY BUGS, VIRUSES, TROJAN HORSES, OR THE LIKE, WHICH MAY BE TRANSMITTED TO OR THROUGH OUR SERVICES BY ANY THIRD PARTY, AND/OR (V) ANY ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN ANY CONTENT OR FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE OF ANY KIND INCURRED AS A RESULT OF YOUR USE OF ANY CONTENT POSTED, EMAILED, TRANSMITTED, OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE VIA THE SERVICES, WHETHER BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT, OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY, AND WHETHER OR NOT THE COMPANY IS ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. THE FOREGOING LIMITATION OF LIABILITY SHALL APPLY TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW IN THE APPLICABLE JURISDICTION.11. IndemnityTo the extent permitted by applicable law, you agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Prometheum Institute, its officers, directors, employees and agents, from and against any and all claims, damages, obligations, losses, liabilities, costs or debt, and expenses (including but not limited to attorney’s fees) arising from: (i) your use of and access to the Service; (ii) your violation of any term of these Terms of Service; (iii) your violation of any third party right, including without limitation any copyright, property, or privacy right; or (iv) any claim that your Content caused damage to a third party. This defense and indemnification obligation will survive these Terms of Service and your use of the Service.
12. Ability to Accept Terms of Service
You affirm that you are either more than 18 years of age, or an emancipated minor, or possess legal parental or guardian consent, and are fully able and competent to enter into the terms, conditions, obligations, affirmations, representations, and warranties set forth in these Terms of Service, and to abide by and comply with these Terms of Service. In any case, you affirm that you are over the age of 13, as the Service is not intended for children under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use the Service.
© 2016 Prometheum Institute. All rights reserved.
FAQ
Privacy Policy
Terms of Service
CONTACT
